（忆往昔）
你好 艾米
Hi, Amy.
你了解我 知道我是个什么样的人
You know me. You know the kind of person I am.
她杀了很多人 所以我们就得杀她
She's dropping bodies, man, which means we got to drop her.
她收手了 相信我
She's done. Trust me.
好吧
Okay.
你改不了你的本性 你还会再杀人的
You are what you are. You will kill again.
你到底怎么回事
What's going on with you?
你改不了你的本性
You are what you are.
你究竟想说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
我是指你不想说的那件心事
I'm talking about whatever you're not telling me about.
我知道你并不想放她走的
I know you didn't want to let her go,
但把她放走是对的
but it was the right thing to do.
- 谢谢你 - 不客气
- So, thanks. - No problem.
你知道我的座右铭 为人民服务
You know my motto … "Here to help."
那你是怎么对艾米的
Kind of like you helped Amy?
对不起
I'm sorry.
你还是一个人走吧
You should just go on without me.
好吧
All right.
（如今）
是的
Yes.
已经有一个幽灵来到我们身边
A spirit has gathered around us.
你在这儿吗 幽灵
Are you with us, spirit?
我感觉到了
I feel something.
我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
I have goose bumps.
是丹尼叔叔吗
Uncle Danny?
现在我们要与他接触了
We're going to make contact now.
把你们的手放在占卜板上
Rest your hands on the planchette.
让幽灵来指引它们
Let the spirit guide our hands.
噢 幽灵啊
O spirit,
你是我们要找的人吗
Are you the one we seek?
你是
Are you…
丹尼叔叔吗
Uncle Danny?
我没使劲
I'm not doing that.
当然 是她在推
Yeah. She's pushing it.
有所怀疑很正常
It's okay to be skeptical.
丹尼 如果你在这儿的话
Danny, if you're with us,
请敲两下表示肯定
Knock twice for yes.
丹尼
Danny?
你能问问他 他快乐吗
Can you ask him, is he happy?
是的 他很快乐
He is. He's happy.
莎迪跟他在一起吗
Is Sadie with him?
你真是太离谱了 辛西娅
Now you're being ridiculous, Cynthia.
谁会在乎莎迪啊
Who cares about Sadie?
哎呀 是的
Ah, yes.
我看到了
I see…
一只小宠物
A family pet.
就是她 莎迪是一只雪纳瑞犬
That's her. Sadie was a schnauzer.
她跟丹尼 在那边也在追网球玩儿
She's with Danny, chasing tennis balls in the afterlife.
莎迪非常喜欢网球
Sadie loved tennis balls.
有一些重要的文件
There were important papers.
谁都找不到 没放在保险箱里
No one can find them. They weren't in the safe.
你能向他打听下
Can you just ask him…
当然没问题
Of course.
你得把手跟我一起放在占卜板上
I'll need you to place your hands with me on the planchette.
也许
Maybe …
也许是丹尼不太喜欢这个问题
maybe Danny didn't like the question.
叫他少跟哥兜圈子
Tell him to quit fooling around.
他心知肚明那可是我的钱
He knows darn well that's my money.
你俩就不能消停一下吗
Can't you two stop squabbling?
拜托了 他都已经死了
For pete's sake, he's dead.
告诉他我们很抱歉
Tell him we're sorry.
也许如果我们友好点儿 他就能
Maybe if we're nice, he'll …
偶滴神啊
Oh, my god.
丹尼
Danny?
（不是）
怎么回事
What's going on?
快逃
Run!
[邪恶力量 第7季第7集]
（无新信息）
天啊 还真够邋遢的
Geez. Have some pride.
好了
Yeah.
还真是让我饥饿难耐
That make me hungry.
你在收听的是香蕉大哥给你带来的《晨叨》
You're listening to the Morning Chaos with me, Bananas Foster.
听你个大头鬼 傻帽
The hell I am, ass-hat.
接下来是一则诡异的新闻
And now for the news of the weird …
准确地说 是两起非常诡异的谋杀
two very odd murders, to be exact.
灵媒镇的灵媒被杀
Mediums are dying in Lily Dale,
灵媒镇是全美最灵异的小镇
the most psychic town in America.
所以如果你想预知自己的未来
So if you want to know your future,
还是找警察吧 总不会只有我想到
stick to that 900 line, 'cause is it me,
这些家伙不是该能预测到未来吗
or should those guys have seen it coming?
（纽约州 灵媒镇）
哦伟大的幽灵啊
O spirits of the further…
我能中劲球彩票吗
Am I going to win the Powerball?
哥要发财了
I'm gonna be rich.
（灵媒镇年度）
（伊美黛·格瑞文 高迪奶奶 尼克莱·李希安）
（灵媒节）
（恩典咖啡屋 给予你独一无二的一天）
你好
Hello!
第一次来恩典咖啡屋吧
First time at good graces?
没错
Yes.
本店之售本地出产食物 生物动力更绿色
Well, we're 100% locally sourced, biodynamic,
而你每点一餐可得到免费箴言一条
and you get a free affirmation with every order.
我去找个玉米卷摊好了
Think I'll source a taco joint.
就要一杯咖啡吧 浓郁黑咖
Just coffee, black, extra shot.
你总是穿西服去看手相吗
You always wear a suit to get your palm read?
也是 你能跑来也是意料之中
Yeah. Not surprised you caught this one.
美国早间新闻都播了
It's on every morning zoo in America.
能坐下吗
You mind?
我 我去过现场了
So, I, uh, I went to the scene.
电线 音响 电磁读数都高得吓人
Wires, speakers, enough E.M.F. to make your hair stand up.
给本别想得到净读数
Don't even think about getting a reading.
如果不是死了两个灵媒的话
Oh, and, uh, if this hadn't have been two psychics that bit it…
我就会把这当做倒霉的意外了
I would have just chalked this up as being dumb and accidental.
当然我知道 我懂
And I know, I know.
这个镇子都是做招鬼的
This whole town's supposedly calling ghosts.
但那是需要很厉害的巫术和咒语
But that takes some serious spellwork and some serious mojo.
而那女人唯一的一本书却是奥普拉的
The only books this lady had were Oprah crap.
你上次碰到真正的灵媒是什么时候
When was the last time you actually saw a real psychic?
帕梅拉
Huh? Pamela?
米苏丽
Missouri?
不管怎样 我们重聚也是好事 你好吗
Anyway, this is good. And, uh, how you been?
你想吃点儿什么呢
And what can I get for you?
薄煎饼 里脊肉 黑咖啡
Uh, pancakes, side of pig. Coffee, black.
好的
Fantastic.
你是神祗的男性体现
You are a virile manifestation of the divine.
他该死的说哥什么呢
What the hell did he say to me?
哦 很好笑吗
Oh, it's funny?
行 没事 你笑吧 萨姆 真滑稽
Yeah, no. Go ahead. Laugh it up, Sam. Hilarious.
迪恩
Dean…
你终于开口了
Oh, he speaks.
听着
Look…
萨姆
Sam.
听着 我们都到这儿了
Look, we're both here.
这边还在死人
All right, the chance of either one of us leaving.
我们就都不会离开
while people are still dying out there …
你不如忍耐一下跟我一起搞定这件事
you might as well bite the bullet and work with me on this one.
我不知道我能不能做到
I don't know if I can.
这不算是什么难事
I'm not asking you to open up a can of worms.
行吗 我都没问你
Okay, I'm not even asking you.
你过去的一周半到底去哪儿了
Where the hell you've been for the past week and a half.
很好
Good.
我的意思是 咱们一起阻止杀戮
I'm just saying, let's try and stop the killings.
没别的
That's it.
好吧
Okay.
可以吗 很好
Okay? Good.
有什么事吗
Can I help you?
你们是那两兄弟…
You're the brothers from the …
不是 不是
Oh, no, no, no, no.
几周前新闻里的温彻斯特兄弟吗
The Winchester guys on the news a couple weeks back?
- 我们被认错很多次了 - 我们不是
- No … we get that a lot. - Yeah, no.
那俩没人性的杀人狂已经被制裁了
Those depraved killers got put down like the dogs that they were.
我们和他们不同 完全无公害
Oh. Us on the other hand, we're completely harmless.
当然啦
Oh, yeah!
对不起 我犯傻了
I'm sorry. Silly me.
从你们的气场就能看出来 你们很温和
And I can see by your energies, you're completely gentle.
二位请见谅 她很容易激动
Excuse my friend. She's excitable.
亲爱的 看清楚了 他们是联调局探员
Sweetheart, look at them, hmm? They're FBI.
我是俄罗斯人 一眼就能认出执法人员
I'm Russian. We can spot the law.
你们是来调查那两起惨案的吧
You must be here about the tragedies.
我们对发生的事感到十分不安
Oh, we're just beside ourselves about what happened.
是啊 而且快要过节了嘛
Yeah. And so close to festival season, huh?
是啊 不是
Yeah … no …
我们当然也会担心
Of course we are worried.
但不知道那是怎么回事
We have no idea what's going on, huh?
我叫尼克莱 需要我帮忙尽管找我
Nikolai. Let me know if I can help you.
我的直觉力很强
I'm highly intuitive.
尼克莱·李希安 掰勺师
Nikolai Lishin, spoon bender?
世界知名哦
World famous.
来灵媒节看我的演示吧
Come to my demonstration at the festival, huh?
我教你怎么利用思想的力量
I teach you to harness the power of your mind.
走吧 别打扰他们了
Come, let's leave them be.
这真是个度假的好地方啊 是吧
So glad we decided to vacation here, huh? Right?
好了 看看吧
All right. Here we go.
第一位死者
First death.
第二位死者
Second death.
有什么重点
What am I looking at?
看到这个没
Well, see this?
这是一号死者 伊美黛·格瑞文
Now, this is Imelda Graven, Death Number One.
她被自己的水晶球砸中头部而死
She was brained by her own crystal ball.
既无奈又讽刺
Bummer, and ironic.
同一条项链吗
Same necklace?
是的 伊美黛在遗嘱中把它留给了高迪
Yeah. See, Imelda gave it to Goldy in her will.
好 这东西可能被诅咒了
Okay, so, cursed object, maybe?
值得调查一下
Worth looking into.
高迪的近亲住在镇上 也是个灵媒
Goldy's next of kin lives in town, also a psychic.
好的 我的咖啡还没端来
Oh, good. I haven't had my fill.
他把我的勺子掰弯了
He broke my spoon.
你是梅勒妮·高迪吗
Melanie Golden?
你好 现在有空吗
Hi. Uh…Got a minute?
需要我留下陪你吗
You want me to stay?
不用了 没事
No, that's okay.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢你过来看我 亲爱的
Thanks for stopping by, hon.
应该的
Of course.
她是我朋友
A friend.
刚刚听说我奶奶的事
She just heard about my grandmother…
我猜你们也是为这事来的吧 请进吧
Which is, I guess, why you guys are here, so come on in.
不好意思 我刚到家
Sorry. I just got back.
你出城了吗
You were out of town?
是的 我来回跑 旅馆会场两点一线
Yeah, I work the circuit … hotels, conventions, you know.
等等
Oh. Wait.
无意冒犯 不过…
No offense, but…
你看着不像灵媒
You don't seem all that psychic.
为什么这么说
Why do you say that?
我是说 你们家没有…
Well, I mean, just, you know, where's all the…
水晶球和金字塔
Crystals and pyramids?
我下班了
I'm off the clock.
而且我也不是灵媒
Also not psychic.
怎么了 这是个正当职业
What? It's an honest living.
好一个「正当」
Interesting definition of "honest."
我真的能读懂人的想法
Well, I honestly read people.
不是靠装神弄鬼 而是通过肢体语言
It's just less whoo-whoo, more body language.
比如说你们俩
Like you two …
搭档很久了 但是…
Longtime partners, but, um…
关系非常紧张
A lot of tension.
你很生气
You're pissed.
你压力很大
And you're stressed.
不算很难
It's not brain surgery.
就因为这个 我和奶奶合不来
It's kind of why my grandma and me didn't get along.
别看她平时净说些唬人的话
I mean, she'd go full smoke-machine,
但还真的相信那些鬼神之事
but she still actually believed in all that stuff, so…
你不信吗
You don't?
你信吗
You do?
我很开通的
I've got an open mind.
说出来吓你一跳
You'd be surprised.
很抱歉 有件事情要问你
I'm sorry to have to ask,
你奶奶有条项链
but there's a necklace of your grandmother's.
不在我手上
Don't have it.
她的所有东西都送去百货店了
Everything went straight to the emporium.
她和那个老板商量好的
She had a deal with the owner.
百货店
The emporium?
你们在找…
You're looking…
某样东西
for something.
你真厉害
You're good.
你是「预言师吉米」吗
You "Jimmy Tomorrow"?
我们在找一条项链
We're looking for a necklace.
真浪漫
Oh. Romantic.
是随高迪奶奶的遗物送过来的
It would have come in with Grandma Goldy's effects.
是啊 没错
Oh. Yes, yes.
你们知道这是塞萨利之珠吧
Now, you do know that this is the Orb of Thessaly.
我们不知道
We did not know.
法力非凡
Very powerful,
十分罕见
very rare.
我猜价格也不菲吧
Let me guess. Very expensive.
绝对物有所值
Worth every penny.
既然如此
Well, in that case,
我们就把它当做证物征用了
we'll be taking the state's-evidence discount.
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
这是谋杀调查
A murder investigation.
我们要谢谢你没有妨碍公务
that we'd like to personally thank you for not obstructing.
要知道 我做私人看相
You know, I give private energetic readings.
不必了 谢谢
No, thanks.
你失去了什么 这令你不堪重负
A loss weighs on you.
你很生气
You're angry.
情况很复杂
It's complicated.
有空来找我 探员
Come see me, agent.
（预言师吉米 私人看相师）
谢谢你 吉米 回见
Thanks, Jimmy. We'll see you.
调查局会按价赔偿这条项链吧
The Bureau's gonna reimburse me for the necklace, right?
我们会给你寄支票的
Oh, we'll send you a check.
好
Right.
他分析你的时候 有点像《超感警探》啊
Went a little "Mentalist" on you there, didn't he?
好了 下个问题 塞萨利之珠是什么
All right. Next question. What's an Orb of Thessaly?
我只知道 这玩意是台湾制造
I know one thing … it's made in Taiwan.
在这种地方碰上假货 真稀奇啊
Oh, a fake, around here. Imagine that.
也就是说杀害灵媒的凶手
'course, that means that whatever's killing mediums.
还在逍遥法外
is still out there.
他当时用意念把那些叉子掰弯就好了
He probably should have bent those with the power of his mind.
警长
Chief.
- 我们在警局见过 - 没错 早上好 特工
- We met at the station. - Right. Morning, agent.
早上好 这位是伯恩特工
Morning. Uh, this is agent Borne.
怎么回事
So, what happened?
挺诡异的 胸腔插满了刀叉
It's a weird one. Chest full of cutlery.
好的 我们四处察看一下
All right. We're gonna take a look around.
发现了什么线索告诉我们一声
Let us know if you get any leads.
我线索倒是不少
Oh, I got leads coming out of my ass.
现在才九点 我们的热线已经接了46通电话
It's 9:00, our tip line had 46 calls,
都是开了天眼的人说他们知道发生了什么
all from clairvoyants that know what really happened.
现在流行的说法是什么
What's the popular theory?
不是鬼魂就是
It's a toss-up between a ghost.
某种专门袭击俄罗斯人的食人恶魔
and some sort of ogre that only attacks Russians.
维持灵媒镇的太平看来挺有趣
Policing Lily Dale sounds fun.
不在这儿就得去洛杉矶了
It was either this or Los Angeles.
那么 这些开了天眼的有没有详细说明
So, these clairvoyants, did they give any details.
为什么他们认定是鬼魂作案
as to why they thought it was a ghost?
或者是…
Or a…
俄罗斯食人恶魔
Russian ogre?
他们听幽灵说的
Their spirit monkey said so.
还有 这个人声称
Plus, apparently, this guy claims.
他曾看到自己死亡的幻象
he had a vision of his own death,
刀叉什么都看到了
cutlery and all.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你好
Hello?
是伯恩特工吗 我是梅勒妮·高迪
Agent Borne? It's Melanie Golden.
还好吗
Everything okay?
你说你很开通是真心话吗
Did you mean it when you said you had an open mind?
我到今天才查看语音信箱
I hadn't checked it until today.
唯一往我的座机上打电话的
I mean, the only person who ever called my landline.
就是我的奶奶
was my grandma.
好的 继续
That's okay. Go on.
我不敢说这就靠谱
Look, I wouldn't put any stock in it.
我是说 她经常打电话来
I mean, she was always calling me.
跟我说那些她确信是种征兆的疯狂的梦
with some crazy dream she was sure was a sign,
诸如此类的事情 可是…
that kind of thing, but…
尼克莱真的看到了自己死亡的幻象吗
Uh, is it true Nikolai had a real vision of his death?
据说是这样
That's what we were told.
她也见过 就在她死掉的那天
Well, so did she … the day she died.
她说什么了
What'd she say?
你可以听听看
Well, you can listen to it if you want.
她说她当时在招魂
She said she was in a seance,
接着灯亮了 十分寒冷
then the lights go, it's freezing.
等等 她这么说了吗 房间里面变冷了
Wait, she said that? That the room got cold?
是的 怎么了 这很重要吗
Yeah. Why? Is that important?
怎么了 那是什么
What? What is it?
鬼魂
A ghost.
不是闹着玩的
The real deal.
不是吧
Come on.
你们是认真的
You're serious.
没错 有瞎编装神弄鬼的把戏
Yeah. See, there's, uh, fake whoo-whoo crap,
但也有真神真鬼的把戏
and there's real whoo-whoo crap.
没错 可是…
Well, yeah, but…
鬼魂吗
Ghosts?
相信我
Oh, trust me.
比这还诡异的事情多了去了
There's a lot weirder out there than that.
那么《X档案》里面讲的是真的
So "The X-Files" is real,
还是你们就是不打联调局的官腔了
or you just stopped talking like an FBI agent.
其实…
Well, um…
我们并不是联调局特工
We're not FBI agents.
我需要喝一杯
I need a drink.
好主意
I support that.
如果这是一个幽灵干的
You know, if this is a spirit,
那它跟一般附在房子上的鬼魂不一样
it ain't your average spook tied to a house.
这东西在整个城镇上游走
I mean, this thing is boogieing all over town.
并不意外
Not surprised.
你说整个灵媒镇
I mean, how many crystal balls.
有多少颗水晶球
do you figure there are in Lily Dale?
大概在五十到全世界所有之间吧
Somewhere between 50 and, uh, all of them.
水晶可以充当召唤幽灵的天线 对吗
Well, I mean, quartz can act as an antenna for spirits, right?
这也是灵媒会
I mean, that's why mediums.
开始使用水晶球的原因
started using crystal balls in the first place.
也就是说这镇上的每一个灵媒店
Well, that means that every storefront in town.
都装了一个鬼魂卫星天线
has got a ghost satellite dish.
没错
Exactly.
这地方到处是招鬼的人
And this place is packed with people summoning spirits.
是的 可是这当中的大部分人
Yeah, but, dude, most of these guys.
甚至连的士都打不到
can't even call a taxi.
只要招来一个就够了
All it takes is one.
这就好像
That's gonna be like.
在一堆萝卜里挑人参啊
looking for a needle in a stack of fake needles.
比这还糟
It's worse.
我敢打赌
I mean, I'll bet you anything.
这些人里有人是有真本事的
some of these guys got real juice.
或许没到杀人那么厉害
I'm not talking kill-people level.
但也足够使事情变得复杂
I'm just saying, enough to make it complicated.
我讨厌这镇子
I hate this town.
好了 怎么样
All right, so, what?
向克丽奥斯小姐（美国著名灵媒）求助吗
Start hitting up the Miss Cleos?
我在想不如分开排查的好
I was thinking split up and canvass.
这样更快
It's faster.
对 你当然这么想了
Right. 'course you were.
怎么了
What is it?
我哥哥吗
My brother?
他又要入狱了吗
Is he going back to prison?
离他远点
Stay away.
他的诅咒会把你拖下水
His curse will drag you down.
要知道有的人会把进监狱变成习惯
Folks do turn jail into a habit, you know?
别别别
Oh, no, no.
不要焦急
Don't fret.
我常说
I's always say,
家人…
family…
反正也让人讨厌
is a pain in the ass anyhow!
谢谢你 喜碧朵姐姐
Thank you, sister Thibideaux.
不对 孩纸
No, child.
要谢谢那些幽灵
Thank the spirits.
那你是给现金还是刷卡
Now, will that be cash or credit?
没事的
It's okay.
我在电话里说了 他能帮上忙
Like I said on the phone, he can help.
冒牌执法者是吧
Phony lawman, huh?
是啊 这里就没有冒牌货了
Yeah, 'cause nobody can relate to phony around here.
如果你能帮上什么忙
Well, if you can do something,
你说你是教皇我都不管
I don't care if you call yourself the pope.
好了 到底发生什么事了
All right. What happened, exactly?
我看到了一个可怕的幻象
What happened is, I had a friggin' vision.
有东西冲着我来
Something is coming for me.
什么东西 你看清楚了吗
What's coming? Did you get a look?
没有
No.
可是当它开始掐断我骨头时 我能分明地感觉到它
But I sure felt it when it started breaking my bones.
我不想死
I don't want to die.
好的 我们会解决的
Okay. We'll figure it out.
你是在这看到那些幻象的吗
The vision happened in here?
是的 在钱箱边
Yeah, by the cash box.
那个「帅哥」可能拍下来了吗
There any chance good-lookin' was watching?
那是什么
What was that?
怎么回事
What the hell?!
我的天呐
Oh, my god.
oh, my god!
那是…一个真正的
W-was that, I mean, an actual …
是的 名副其实的幽灵
Bona fide. Yeah.
无意冒犯
Well, no offense,
但是这里没人看到什么幻象
but nobody's having psychic visions around here.
一切都是这个幽灵搞出来的
This, uh, spirit, whoever she is, is giving them out.
然后再去杀人吗
And then killing people?
除非我们阻止她
Until we stop her.
不过 好消息是
Well, the good news is.
你说看到一个时钟而且它指向了两点
you said you saw a clock and it read 2:00 a.m.,
所以我们还有点时间
so that gives us a little time.
你们有谁认识这个女人吗
Now, does anybody recognize this chick?
我确定我见过她
You know, I swear I've seen her,
好像是在某幅油画见过
like in a painting or something.
油画吗 比如
A painting? Like, a …
不 不是油画
No, not a painting.
在博物馆里的某张老照片里见过
In one of those old photos in the museum.
多年来 灵媒镇就是通灵人士的避难所
Lily Dale has long been a haven for the psychically gifted.
在别处受尽折磨的人 在此受到欢迎
Tortured elsewhere, they're embraced here.
我的家族也有点小小的能力
My own family has a modest natural gift.
我们也有悠久而多彩的历史 并以此为荣
We also celebrate our long and colorful history of…
那就是记录灵异事件
embellishers.
灵的外在形象 拍摄于1890年
Ectoplasm illusion, circa 1890.
（兄妹联手）
这些兄弟姐妹的联合总是没什么好下场
Never ended well for the siblings.
为什么
Why is that?
一起工作带来的压力
Mm, the strain of working together,
或许只是因为他们一生都与彼此相伴
or maybe just being around each other all their lives.
不过这两个人可是个例外 坎贝尔兄弟
Those two were the exception, actually … the Campbells.
关系出名得好
Got along famously.
当然 那只是他们的艺名
Of course, that was just a stage name.
他们不是真的亲兄弟
They weren't actually brothers.
那只是他们的伪装 用以掩盖
That was a cover for their, um…
他们非传统的生活方式
alternative lifestyle.
我还能解答你们什么问题吗
Any other questions I can answer?
是的 她们是谁
Yes. Who are they?
她们是福克斯姐妹 也是灵媒镇的创始人
Oh, the Fox sisters … among the founders of Lily Dale.
凯特·福克斯
Kate Fox …
多苦多难
quite troubled, apparently,
但在台上极具魅惑
but mesmerizing onstage.
据说她可以隔空取物
She's said to be able to levitate objects.
预知人的生死
and foretell one's death.
就是那边那个
That's her.
她的姐姐 玛格丽特
Her older sister, Margaret …
没有什么通灵的能力
perhaps not a natural psychic.
那就是神棍
So, full of crap.
算是吧
Yes, well…
虽然她没有她妹妹的能力
She didn't have her sister's charisma,
但她照看着凯特
but she looked after Kate.
有时候 一个人真正的天赋是照顾别人
Sometimes, one's true gift is taking care of others.
那她们后来怎么样了
So, what happened to them?
一直住在这里
Lived here all their lives.
生活在这儿 也死在这儿吗
Lived here and died here?
是的 埋在公墓里
Yes, well… buried in the cemetery.
很好 受教了
Great. That was very educational.
谢谢
Thank you.
迪恩
Dean.
对不起
I'm sorry.
通常我不在上班时间干这个
I don't normally do this during business hours,
你认识叫埃莉诺
but do you know an Eleanor…
或者埃伦的人吗
or an Ellen?
她似乎很担心你
She seems quite concerned about you.
她想告诉你
She wants to tell you …
请原谅我
pardon me …
如果你不告诉某人情况到底有多糟
if you don't tell someone how bad it really is,
她会穿越灵界踢死你
she'll kick your ass from beyond.
你终究得重新相信某人
You have to trust someone again eventually.
不管怎么样 别忘了来礼品店逛逛
Anyway, don't forget to visit the gift shop.
好吧
All right.
去墓地 挖凯特
Hit up the graveyard, dig up Kate?
等等
All right. Wait a second.
所有证据都指向她了 迪恩
All signs point to her, Dean.
不 给我等等
No. Just hold on a damn minute.
别管什么「事实」了
Enough with "just the facts."
我们说好
We agreed …
不 我们说好一起查这件事
No, we agreed to work the case.
我们没说好你可以一直臭着脸
We didn't agree for you to be a dick the whole time.
什么
What?
你在生我气 对吗
You're pissed, okay?
- 你也有权生气 - 当然了
- And you've got a right. - Yeah, damn straight.
- 但你也够了吧 - 谁说的
- But enough's enough. - Says who?
听着 我会继续查这个案子
Look, I'll work this damn case,
但你对我撒谎 杀了我的朋友
but you lied to me, and you killed my friend.
不 我只是杀了一个血染四命的怪物
No, I put down a monster who killed four people,
如果你不认识她的话 你也会这么做
and if you didn't know her, you'd have done the Same thing.
我认识她 迪恩
I did know her, Dean.
是啊 所以你才下不了手
Yeah, which is why you couldn't do it.
听着 我理解
Look, I get it.
世界上就是有些人
There are certain people in this world,
不管他们是多么危险 你就是下不了手
no matter how dangerous they are, you just can't.
别来这套 都是废话
Don't pull that card. That's bull.
如果说我长了什么教训
Look, if I've learned one thing,
那就是什么事感觉不对
it's that if something feels wrong,
那它很有可能就是错的
it probably is!
通常来说没错 但杀死艾米可没错
Usually, yeah. But killing Amy was not wrong.
你下不了手 所以我来
You couldn't do it, so I did.
这就是家人 为你干脏活儿
That's what family does … the dirty work.
我也会把事情全部告诉你的
And I would have told you eventually,
但我得确认你发神经「举枪打撒旦」的事
once I knew that this whole "waving a gun at satan" thing.
以后不会再犯了
was a one-time show.
我认为这不算无理的要求
I think it's reasonable to want to know.
我有权知道你是不是还疯着 萨姆
that you're off the friggin' high dive, Sam.
你差点把我们都害死
You almost got us both killed,
你大可随意发火
so you can be pissed all you want,
但别再唧唧歪歪
but quit being a bitch.
我懂她为什么杀人
I get why she's killing people.
我不懂为什么她先警告他们
I don't get why she's warning them.
或许是让他们常常诅咒的滋味
Give them a taste of the curse, maybe?
这可没什么乐趣
It couldn't have been a joyride.
来吧
Here we go.
萨姆
Sam!
走开 疯女人
Back off, crazy eyes.
听我说
Listen to me.
为什么没人听我说
Why isn't anybody listening?
不
No.
这事你说了不算
You don't get a vote.
不 住手
No! Stop!
不
No!
好时机
Nice timing.
好的
Got it.
谢谢你 迪恩
And, Dean, thanks.
他们都弄好了
They took care of it.
那
Okay, so…
就直接回家了吗
What … just go home?
应该是吧
I guess.
你愿意来跟我住上几天吗
Hey, why don't you come stay with me a couple days?
谢谢
Thanks.
再等一会儿
Just one more minute.
没事的 亲爱的
It's fine, hon.
如果你看到那些幻象
Oh, if you had that vision,
你也不想呆在这儿的
You wouldn't want to be here either.
卡蜜尔 没事的 我们快走就是了
Camille, it's okay. Let's just go.
怎么了
What is it?
再给他们打电话 快
Call them back! Now!
梅勒妮
Melanie?
迪恩 你们得回来
Dean, you have to come back.
怎么回事
What's going on?
还是出事了
It's still happening!
等等 什么叫还是
Wait, what do you mean it's …
她还是要来 快告诉我该做点什么
She's still coming! Just tell me what the hell to do!
好吧 听我说 冷静下来
All right. Listen to me. Calm down.
迪恩 把电话给我 你好好开车
Dean, just give me the phone and drive.
梅勒妮 去厨房
Melanie? Hey. Get to the kitchen.
好的
Okay.
她来了
She's here!
只管去厨房 找些盐来
All right, just go. Get salt.
起作用了 她走了
It worked. She's gone!
不 她又回来了
No, she's back!
盐用完了
I'm out of salt!
找铁器 有壁炉吗
Find iron. Is there a fireplace?
梅勒妮
Melanie!
天啊 梅尔
Oh, god! Mel!
卡蜜尔 卡蜜尔
Camille! Camille!
卡蜜尔 不要
Camille! No!
我们早该知道那个「好妹妹 坏姐姐」的故事
Should have known that whole "Good sis, bad sis" story.
是揽客手段
was just showmanship crap.
结果凯特只是想警告人们
Oh, and it turns out that Kate was just trying to warn people.
她妹妹才是那个邪恶的婊子
about her evil bitch sister.
而我们却一把火烧得她灰飞烟灭
And we burned her bones,
这回没人警告我们了
so that's gone.
- 迪恩 - 干嘛
- Dean. - What?
我们现在能做的就是阻止她
All we can do now is go stop her.
这主意真不好 离好主意差远了
That's not good enough, by a mile.
相信我 我也知道 但是
I know. Believe me. But …
我们能不能晚点再说
Can we talk about this later?
你还好吧
How you holding up?
不太好
Been better.
如果你要我们离开的话
Listen, if you need for us to leave …
我要你们俩离开
I need you guys to leave.
好 我们会走的
Okay, we will.
只不过
It's just that…
玛格丽特还在外面兴风作浪
Look … Margaret is still out there.
你们想知道些什么
What do you guys need to know?
昨晚有没有发生什么特别的事
Is there anything that stood out?
她几乎看都没看我一眼
She barely gave a crap about me.
我好像只是挡路了
I mean, I was just in the way.
她只想抓住卡蜜尔
She was all about getting Camille.
- 好的 有点线索了 - 还有件事
- Okay. That's something. - One other thing.
她很享受
Um…She enjoyed it.
她当时在笑
She was smiling.
大白天的做这事也太暴露了
I feel naked doing this in daylight.
快点就是了
Yeah. Let's just hurry up.
好了 玛格斯
All right, Mags.
这次我的打火机可已经加过油了
My lighter's juiced this time.
太棒了
Geraldo'd.
情况不妙啊
Not good.
一向都是
Never good.
迪恩 如果有人知道要偷走玛格丽特的尸骨
Dean, if someone knew enough to take Margaret's bones,
那可不是闹着玩的
they're not kidding around.
那是很厉害的捆绑咒
That's serious binding magic.
太好了
Great.
灵媒贱鬼被人控制了
Psychic ghost bitch on a leash.
我们得找到她的尸骨
We got to find those bones.
那我们就得找到那个笨蛋
So we got to find the bonehead.
那怎么办
So, what?
打电话给鲍比 查查如何控制鬼魂的力量吗
We call Bobby, see what it takes to harness the power of a ghost?
好
Yeah.
萨姆 你知道为什么我不要把钱花在
Hey, Sam, you know why I'm not going to spend my money.
灵媒镇一年一度的灵媒节
at the annual Lily Dale E.S.P. Festival.
还有今年的吃热狗比赛上吗
and Hot-Dog-Eating Contest this year?
还真想不出来
Can't imagine.
因为所有的头牌都死了
Because all the headliners are dead.
（灵媒节）
尼克莱死后
You know, after Nikolai…
他们让卡蜜尔来接替他的位子
they asked Camille to take his spot.
她广受欢迎
I mean, she's so popular.
生前广受欢迎
Was so popular.
所有的死者 你会说他们是
Okay, all these people … would you say that they're.
是镇上最好的灵媒吗
the, uh, you know, top dogs in town?
也不能这么说
Well, it's not really like that.
不过他们的确很受欢迎 就像你奶奶
But they were all doing well. I mean, your grandma?
她是写过几本书
She wrote a few books.
伊美黛也上过两次《内特·博克斯秀》
Yeah, and Imelda was on "The Nate Berkus Show" twice,
我想他们的确很受欢迎
So, yeah, I guess they were doing pretty well.
你觉得这就是她追杀他们的原因吗
You think that's why she went after them?
如果让你猜的话
I mean, if you had to guess,
你觉得谁会是下一个上榜的人呢
who do you think would be next in line?
我不知道
I mean, I don't know.
你的奶奶都上海报了
Well, your grandma was headlining at the big hall,
所以快想想他们会让谁接替她的位子
So who do you think they would ask to fill in for her?
可能是
Probably…
我
…me.
特工 你是来把支票给我的吗
Agent. Are you here with my check?
我来找一个到你这里来买过东西的人
I'm looking for someone who bought some things from you.
你怎么知道是从我这里买的
How do you know from me?
我想加油站是不会卖灰木圣坛的
I'm kind of doubting they sell ash-wood altars at the gas 'n sip.
确实
Valid.
让我看看这张单子
Let me see the list.
有了 信用卡支付收据
Ah. Here we go. Credit-card receipt.
我想你还要那人的地址吧
I assume you want the address?
那真是太好了 谢谢
That would be great. Thanks.
只是尽我绵薄之力
It's the least I can do.
我刚听说了卡蜜尔·喜碧朵的事
I just heard about Camille Thibideaux.
太感谢了
Thanks a lot.
不客气
You're welcome.
你确定那有效吗
Are you sure that'll work?
应该足够拖住她
That should hold her off long enough.
让萨姆找到她的尸骨然后一把火烧了
for Sam to find the bones and burn them.
希望如此
Hopefully.
Hopefully?
他们会疼吗
Does it hurt 'em?
烧掉他们尸骨的时候
Burning their bones?
我还真没考虑过这事
I never really thought about it.
可能会吧
Probably, yeah.
那就好
Good.
圣坛在哪里
Where's the altar?!
就在那里
It's there!
你
You're…
不是个巫师
not a necromancer.
这是个心理助产班 我发誓
This is a lamaze class, I swear.
我 我相信你
I-I believe you.
抱歉
Sorry.
迪恩 是那个当铺的家伙
Dean, it's the pawn-shop guy.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
他把我骗到一个孕妇瑜伽班去了
He goose-chased me to a friggin' pregnant yoga class.
查出他把她的尸骨藏在哪里了
All right, well, figure out where he put her bones.
我会的
I will.
速度啊 萨姆
Fast, Sam.
（「预言师吉米」 私人看相师 未来是美好的 美国 纽约 灵媒镇 主街 809 1/2）
不知怎的 我就知道你会回来
Somehow, I just knew you'd be back.
你好啊 特工 把头骨放下
Hi, agent. Put the skull down.
好 好 放松 给
Okay, okay. Take it easy. Here.
好了 你该收手了
All right. That's enough.
- 她走了 - 不见得
- Is she gone? - I doubt it.
但是她不能过线的 对吧
But she can't get past the line, right?
对的
Right.
捆绑咒施得不错
Nice binding spell.
你这样无济于事
It doesn't matter.
她是出于自愿帮我的
She helps me because she wants to.
什么
What?
见鬼 我就讨厌他们干这事
Damn it. I hate when they do that.
去拿盐撒圈
Get the salt. Go.
迪恩
Dean!
玛格丽特和我一样
Margaret and me are the same.
我们都有真把式
We're the real thing.
但是你猜怎么
But guess what …
有时候真把式
sometimes the real thing.
并不是那么好看好玩的
just isn't pretty or entertaining enough.
当我向人们展示能力时 他们吓坏了
When I show people what I'm capable of, it scares them.
我连租金都付不出
I can't pay my rent!
到我身后来
Get behind me.
别想往前走了 婊子
That's as far as you go, bitch.
玛格丽特很高兴为我杀人
Margaret's happy to kill for me.
她喜欢束缚
She likes the leash.
你真有病
You're sick.
除此之外呢
You know what else I am?
我还是个真正的灵媒 你个白痴
A real psychic, you dick-bag.
惊喜
Surprise.
对不起 帅哥
Sorry, handsome.
她其他的骨头在哪
Where are the rest of the bones?
那些人命不该死
These people don't deserve to die.
天哪 你在搞笑吗
Oh, come on! Are you kidding me?
就因为我没像他们那样唬人 就该生活困窘吗
I live in squalor cause I can't put on a show like them?
别这么做
Don't do this.
- 骨头在卧室 对吗 - 不对
- They're in the bedroom, aren't they? - No.
你不能过去
You're not getting in there.
迪恩
Dean!
真不幸
Too bad.
在床上
In the bed?
骨头放在床上
They were in the bed?
是的
Yeah.
他居然连骨头都不放过
I can't believe he was boning her.
迪恩
Dean.
还需要点别的吗
Can I get you anything else?
再满一杯吧
Uh, just a refill.
你说什么箴言 我就揍你
And if you affirmate me, I'm gonna punch you in the face.
好吧 咖啡马上到
All righty then. coffee, coming up.
我真想快点摆脱这个算命镇
I can't wait to get out of this frickin' fortune cookie.
迪恩
Dean.
我出去
I'm gonna go, um…
随便逛逛吧
do something outside.
好的
Okay.
请坐吧
Hi. Have a seat.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
你都没给我时间道谢
You didn't stick around so I could say thank you.
不用谢我
No reason to thank me.
你救了我
You saved my life.
但是没救成你朋友
Yeah, but not your friend's.
又不是你召的鬼 所以
You didn't send that ghost, so…
谢谢你来杀了它
Thank you for coming to kill it.
你和萨姆的关系似乎有所缓和
You and sam seem a little better.
这么短时间你就能看出来
You could tell that from the walk up?
信不信由你
Take it or leave it.
我猜你不会再回来了
Also guessing you're not so keen to come visit here again,
所以 这就算道别吧
So…this is goodbye.
真希望我们相遇的这周不这么糟
Wish we'd met on a better week.
我希望我能有一周不这么糟
I wish I had better weeks.
但是 说不准会有呢
But, uh, hey. You never know.
你又不能预知未来 对吧
It's not like you can tell the future, right?
好吧 很模糊
Well, answer's hazy.
以后再试吧
Try again later.
好吧
right.
那是你的东西
That's your stuff.
是啊 我想我们还是坐一辆车吧
Yeah. Yeah. I figured we'd take one car.
我没意见 你还想打残我的脸吗
Works for me. You still want to break my face?
不了 目前不想
No. Not at this moment.
你知道吗
Look, you know what?
你是对的
You were right.
艾米的事
About Amy.
如果她
If she was…
只是个路人妖怪
just any monster,
我就不会那么轻易放她走了
I'm not sure I could have let her walk away.
我也说不好 我永远都不会知道了
I don't know. I mean, I'll never know.
那你是什么意思
So, what are you saying?
我的意思是
What I'm saying is…
我理解你为什么这么做
I get why you did it.
你只是为了保证没有别人会再受伤害
You were just trying to make sure no one else got hurt.
但问题在于
But here's the thing.
你不能就这么看着我
You can't just look me in the face.
对我说你没事
and tell me you're fine.
我是说 你失眠 还大量饮酒
I mean, you're not sleeping, you drink for the record …
又来了
Oh, here we go.
我知道我没资格来说你
Look, whatever. Last one to preach. I know.
但是 跟我说实话
But… just be honest with me.
你这副样子
How are those the actions of someone.
怎么可能分清是非
who knows they did the right thing?
你想听实话
You want me to be honest?
我跟着感觉走
I went with my gut.
而且我感觉不错
And that felt right.
我不信任她 萨姆
I didn't trust her, sam.
自从小卡之后
Of course, ever since cass,
我就很难再相信任何人了
I'm having a hard time trusting anybody.
至于我的行为
And as far as how I been acting…
我不知道
I don't know.
也许是不想对你撒谎
Maybe it's 'cause I don't like lying to you.
感觉不对劲
You know, it doesn't feel right.
所以你猜对了 我最近是很焦虑
So, yeah, you got me there. I been climbing the walls.
这个我有体会
I know how that is.
但是
But, hey…
如果说我从博物馆那里学到了什么
If I learned one thing from that museum,
兄弟联手并非易事
sibling acts are tough.
别把咱俩和那帮疯子比
Oh, don't compare us to that hall of crazy.
跟他们相比 我们就是正常家庭的代言人了
We're like poster kids of functional family life compared to them.
标准有点低
It's a low bar.
曲线分级评分法从幼儿园就助我及格了
Grading on a curve has got me past everything since kindergarten,
就别挑刺了
so don't knock it.
随你吧
Whatever you say.
我还是想知道那家伙怎么弯汤勺的
I still want to know how that guy bent my spoon.
别惦记了 萨姆 这里是灵媒镇
Forget it, sam. It's Lily Dale.